As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take
in the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled!
La la la la la.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky.
Ready now for adventure.
We're itching to try.
Get ready to roam!
So all aboard now we're set to go.
Set sail to the ocean so deep.
Ready for a truly grand adventure.
Well don't you think
that sounds really fun?
All this excitement is second to none.
As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take.
In the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled.
La la la la la.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget.
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set.
Now I won't be scared.
As long as I keep that feeling there.
With that, let us keep up the pace.
While enjoying every
trip from place to place.
Our timid hearts get the rhythm ingrained.
So let's keep going, adventure awaits.
So many treasures await.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices.
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud.
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous.
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
Shadow!
If we keep going forward after that,
we'll hit a giant refrigerator.
That's the last place we saw Moria.
Sounds good!
I thought Perona was supposed
to take care of you, miscreants.
Dr. Hogback!
Eh?
A reindeer?
But why is it talking?
The infamous Dr.
Hogback, I presume.
That guy was hanging out with Moria.
Guess I better kick his ass too!
Let's not be hasty.
Don't do it, Luffy.
I have a bone to pick with this guy.
Let me fight him.
You see that big metal door behind you?
That leads to the refrigerator.
Go on ahead!
Okay, you got it.
How rude!
You can't just ignore me
and waltz your way to Moria?
Get them Shandora.
What's that coming out of you see
dream go on ahead captain, you got it.
Thanks a lot Robin.
I Told you to stop
ignoring me I called back!
You have no right to call
yourself a doctor anymore.
I've lost all respect for you.
False! False! False!
I didn't recognize you
at first, Dr. Chopper.
So you have Zoan-type
Devil Fruit powers, do you?
I must admit you're a
fascinating creature.
I don't know how you
managed to escape after
they carried you through Perona's garden,
but that's irrelevant now.
I found you again, and I won't
let you get away a second time.
Your shadow will be mine.
No.
Rather I should have that interesting
body of yours turned into a marionette?
Alright finally, what is this place?
There you are!
Oh.
You again.
This thing is too freaking huge, brother!
And look at those horns!
Did he climb up from hell or something?
I've never seen anything like this!
It's really a zombie!
Holy crap,
Luffy, it's all over, he's gonna grind
us up and make meat pies out of us!
What is he going to do?
There we go.
Okay, now I look like the real thing.
Happy King of the Pirates
without an awesome hat.
Man, that sure was scary
when that building fell down
What just happened?
Are you telling me that
thing didn't even notice us?
It's hard to believe, but it really
does act like Luffy, doesn't it?
Something that huge with his fighting
power is going to give us hell!
Come on, let's just get out of here.
You guys don't need your shadows, right?
Like hell we don't!
Even if I did give up on
my shadow, which is stupid,
by the way, we'd still have to
rescue Nami, so get your ass up!
The problem right now is that
we're all stuck down here.
The stairs were the only surefire
way to get where we were going,
and they're completely destroyed.
And even if we changed our
route and take this passage,
we're still screwed since
the bridge got taken out too.
In other words, we can't get to that
mansion with the mast either way.
And it's way too far for us to jump.
We had a shortcut laid out for us.
Now we're gonna have to go
some scary way full of zombies.
Just give me 30 seconds.
I got this.
I'm not happy with how
this railing turned out.
You built a bridge!
There was wood and scraps everywhere.
If I couldn't throw together a bridge
or two, I'd be a damn disgrace.
I mean, if you say so, but
for a makeshift bridge,
you should put a lot of
effort into the details.
You're saying you want me to do a
half-assed instruction job, huh?
Nah, don't hear me complaining.
Anyway, thanks a lot.
Let's go
What is a princess live here?
I don't know what I was
expecting, but it wasn't this
I was going to have my zombies grab
you at the stairs by the bridge,
but I suppose that plan fell through.
Ors was just reborn, and
he's already a nuisance.
My patience is running very thin tonight.
It's those ghosts again.
So I was her controlling
them all this time?
What the hell are those things anyway?
Oh my, is that fear I sense in your voice?
I wouldn't blame you after
what happened last time.
I can create ghosts at my command with
the power of the hollow, hollow fruit.
You can think of them as a
sort of extension of myself.
They can empty your heart
and crush your spirit.
This should be fun, for me at least.
I can't believe this little cutie is the
one making those annoying ghost creatures.
Save your comments for another time!
If we get hit by even one of those
things, it's all over for us!
He's right! We gotta run!
I don't want to lose my dignity again.
Negative Hollow!
I'm dumber than a mackerel.
I should just die.
I know, Broke.
I wish a straight dog would step on me.
I should just crawl around on the
ground like a worm and eat dirt.
It's all over.
Capture them.
Well, that was easy.
All that's left are the three above us.
Cat-Blake Salt-Star!
Who did that?
That's my crew, you know.
I won't let you hurt them.
Tricky punk, you acted like you got
hit just so you could surprise me.
Negative ha-ho!
My name is Captain Usa.
I don't get it.
Why don't my attacks do anything to you?
I know I didn't miss that time.
What is this?
What kind of power have you got?
Power has nothing to do with it.
I just naturally have.
A NEGATIVE PERSONALITY!
He's even more negative
than the negative ghosts!
He's a real piece of work!
No!
Mistress Perona!
It can't be!
No human is immune to
the negative hollows!
They have the power to empty your heart.
So long as humans are alive, they're
always looking toward the future,
moving forward one step at a time.
But this man, he...
Don't give up!
Do your best! Don't give up!
Don't pity me!
Time to step out of this!
You gotta go rescue Nami and get the
shadows back before it's too late.
No matter how strong you are, you
don't stand a chance against her!
All you can do is run.
But don't worry, I'll
take care of her for you.
I can't believe it.
Usopp actually looks cool for once.
Is his heart really that empty?
Little turd.
No, but please defeat all
the zombies before you go!
Valiant though I may be.
I must conserve my energy.
All right, see you later.
No, wait.
The zombies.
You've got to beat the zombies.
I can't do that part of my own.
Wait.
Do you Absalom
promise to take Nami
as your lawfully wedded
wife to have and to hold
in good times and in bad?
in sickness and in health?
Damn straight.
Do you, Nami,
promise to take Absalom as your husband to
have and to hold in good times and in bad?
in sickness and in health?
Oh, yes, I sure do.
I think he's so cute.
Then you may now kiss the bride.
That last one must have been a dud.
With this final attack, you'll lose
every last bit of your will to live.
Now, quadruple negative
attack, negative hobbles!
Holy crap!
He took all four ghosts at once!
For as long as Thriller
Bark has floated on the sea!
There's never been a spirit that couldn't
be broken by the negative ghosts.
The negative ghosts
have lost in negativity!
Oh, Kumasi, I'm sorry for everything.
Look, even Mistress Perona's
getting negative now.
What the hell is this guy?
The patron saint of
pessimism or something?
It's freaking me out!
Now listen up,
there's no one not anyone in this entire
world who can defeat me in negativity.
Yeah that was a close
one if he hadn't been
there that would have been
the end for all of us!
Pretty scary power she's
got that's for sure.
Hey I'm gonna run on ahead and
rescue Nami on my own. Gotcha.
Good luck. Go kick some ass. Oh, I will.
I've got the power of love on my side.
Nani swan!
I won't let you get married to me!
Hey, aren't we pretty high
up for him to jump like that?
Maybe, but don't forget,
when the adrenaline kicks in, you
won't feel the pain until later.
Either way, let's get to
the top of that mansion.
Right.
That's where the skeleton guy is.
You rise up like you're a phoenix or
around here a bit more like a zombie.
No matter, you won't be
able to stand much longer.
I'll make sure you stay
down for good this time.
No more of these pointless
efforts to get your shadow back.
Now tell me what part of
that wretched excuse for
a body would you like me
to sever with my arrow?
Not slash.
You don't know the first
thing about that technique.
You have no right to even speak its name.
I used to serve in my
kingdom's raider squad.
The quick draw attack at
which I was most skilled
was originally called the
Requiem the Banderole.
However,
my comrades in arms renamed it in regard
to my own sword fighting technique.
They called it Three Verse
Humming Arrow Notch Slash.
Even if you share my
personality and my techniques,
You've forgotten my memories
and all the feelings
attached to them which means
you will not use that name!
Well if those memories and
feelings make you the real thing
why don't you do something about
it come take down the fake!
This will be your last chance to do so.
Sword Technique 3 verse humming.
Arrow not slash.
No!
Naboo.
More than anything else, I
just want to apologize to you.
And I'm drifting,
drifting all for nothing.
It's so lonely.
My life.
So lonely.
Well, while you're making up your mind!
I think I'll start with this afro.
What's going on?
The entire mansion is shaking! Whoa!
What's up with all this?
Rumbling.
Don't know.
Don't care.
Probably just an earthquake.
Is that the laboratory?
Look!
There's the skeleton guy!
Can you hear me?
Looks like it took quite a beating!
But you're still alive, aren't you?
Say something!
Am I dreaming?
Why are you here?
This won't do!
It all how dare you try to
interfere with our battle?
Not so fast.
Tell me, are you the legendary Samurai
that slayed a dragon in ancient times?
I've been hoping to meet you.
What the hell is going on?
I'm trying to get the closet kissed.
It's kind of a big moment here.
Master Absalom. What is it?
What's with all this shaking?
Thriller Bark has been caught
up in some strange current.
We're being thrown around
all over the place.
The whole island is shaking
How did that happen? Well,
probably because the
special zombie is moving
the rudder without
permission What did you say?
It's moving!
Zombie Generals, listen up!
Move out!
Get out there, find Ours,
and stop him no matter what!
OARS!
That's enough out of
you special zombie oars.
Bring him down!
Start with defeat!
He disappeared. Where'd he go?
How could something that big just...
There's nowhere for him to hide.
There he is, above us!
No, it's not really rubber!
I'm tired of everybody getting
in the way of my flight time!
Annihilated?
You mean the entire group
that just left here?
Uh, yes, sir.
They were squashed flat, all of them.
But that's impossible.
Those guys are the strongest
zombie division on the island.
The zombie general.
Yes, and he took them out instantly.
That can't be.
Isn't Orr supposed to be on our side?
Then why is he revolting against us?
Zombies are made to be obedient.
It's in their nature.
We can't let him keep
up all this rampaging
around if we don't find a way to stop him.
He'll sink the whole island
Is he one of the Straw Hat pirates
Amazing.
He was able to fend off Rium as a tack.
I didn't know he was so strong.
He's the three-sword-style pirate
swordsman of the Straw Hats.
You better believe he's strong.
Looks like he's itching for a fight.
If your pride will allow it,
I think he was planning on
getting your shadow back for you.
What do you say?
My shadow? Really?
Yes, I beg of you!
Whatever you need to do, please get my
shadow back, I'd be ever - Enough already!
Shut the hell up!
Hey, skeleton guy!
That's a really interesting-looking
Cotton you've got there.
You have good eyes.
Yes, this is indeed one of the 21
legendary swords of the highest grade.
A famed black blade with
a reverse wave temperline.
It's known as the clear autumn wind.
Shusui.
Consider yourself fortunate
to cast your eyes on it.
So it is one of the legendary swords.
You're right, I am lucky.
Though I did expect you to have a good
blade, being that you're a samurai and all.
That settles it.
I'm gonna beat you and
take that sword as my own.
Oh, you are so cool! oh